{
  "categories": [],
  "description": "Things that are named after people (eponyms).",
  "difficulty": -1,
  "questions": [{
    "answer": "Cube",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Rubik's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Code",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Morse ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Apple",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Adam's _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Heel",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Achilles' ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "tea",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Earl Grey ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Law",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Murphy's ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Comet",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Halley's _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Prize",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Pulitzer _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Disease",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Lou Gehrig's _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Diet",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Atkins ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Fire",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "St. Elmo's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Tendon",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Achilles' ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Scheme",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Ponzi ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Wall",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Hadrian's ____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Chicken",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "General Tso's _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Number",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Avogadro's ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Salad",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Cobb _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Razor",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Occam's _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Oil",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Lorenzo's ___"
  }, {
    "answer": "Doctrine",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Monroe ________"
  }, {
    "answer": "Effect",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Coriolis ______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Strip",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "MÃ¶bius _____"
  }, {
    "answer": "Paradox",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Zeno's _______"
  }, {
    "answer": "Expedition",
    "category": "Things Named For People Quiz",
    "question": "Shackleton __________"
  }],
  "quizLength": 24,
  "title": "Things Named For People Quiz",
  "url": "http://www.jetpunk.com/quizzes/things-named-for-people-quiz.php"
}